### Tony Z. Torres

(817) 609-7221 | tzepeda.it@gmail.com | Everett, WA

# **Snapshot**

Communicative team-player with a heavy background in hospitality and sales, driven to enter the world of Networking and Security. Completed the CompTIAA+ & Network+, with Security+ and CCNA in progress. Some real-world experience from hands-on college courses and installing SOHO networks for friends/family. Will bring an optimistic and attentive perspective and a continued desire to acquire higher education in IT.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Self-Taught I.T. Student, San Juan Capistrano, CA / Everett, WA

March 2020 - Present

- Student
  - Earned CompTIA A+ and Network+ Certification, passing both by over 90%.
  - Competed 5 college computer courses -- included hands-on network troubleshooting, Cisco device configuration, PC repair, and C++ coding -- receiving an A in all classes.
  - Finished 100+ online simulations (Testout.com) regarding network troubleshooting, help desk tickets, WAN network creation, Active Directory setup, Cisco switch/router configurations, using protocol analyzers etc.

## Online Marketplace Vendor, San Juan Capistrano, CA

January 2017 - December 2020

3rd Party Vendor on Amazon.com and Ebay.com

- Maintained a 99% customer satisfaction score over hundreds of reviews and over 10,000 sales.
- · Increased business efficiency by utilizing multiple software to manage, sell, and reprice thousands of SKUs.
- Initiated and maintained 30+ relationships with local product suppliers -- leading to discounts.

#### Marie Callander's, San Juan Capistrano, CA

June 2008 - December 2016

Food Server

- Trained 30+ new hires and became a dependable trainer due to ability to thoroughly explain procedures and teach efficiency in multitasking.
- · Considered a "Rock Star" server for being able to manage 8+ tables simultaneously while sustaining exemplary service.
- Promoted to Banquet Server, requiring capability to serve a party of 30-100 guests.

# DoorDash Inc., San Juan Capistrano, CA / Everett, WA

September 2020 - Present

Food Delivery

 Upheld a 4.9 customer satisfaction rating and worked part-time to make ends meet while studying for the A+, Network+, and Security+ Certificates.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- · CompTIA A+ (92% Score).
- CompTIA Network+ (90% Score).
- (In Progress) CompTIA Security+ (est. Nov 2021).
- (In Progress) CCNA (est. early 2022).

### **EDUCATION**

# California State University, Fullerton, Fullerton, CA

May 2015

B.A. in Psychology

Honors: Cum Laude.

## Saddleback College, Mission Viejo, CA

February 2012

A.A. in both Psychology & Anthropology

Honors: Cum Laude.

#### **SKILLS**

- Bilingual (Spanish), 1 year of C++, SOHO Installations, Dependable, Avid reader of IT forums, Google Search Operators, Adaptable, Takes Initiative.
- Strong communication skills with customers and non-technical staff, Determined to be an A+ employee, Security Mindfulness.

#### **INTERESTS**

· Chess, Coding Puzzles, Cardio/Strength Exercise, Hiking/Exploring New Trails, Gardening Fruit-Bearing plants, Coffee, Reddit.